Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1963-1977
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-1977
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dale R. Corson papers, 1963-1977.
3-11-1665
Dale R. Corson
134.9 cubic ft.
Office files, correspondence, employment contracts, tape recordings, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The Dale R. Corson papers consist of office files, correspondence, and other material deriving chiefly from his provostship (1963-1969) and presidency of Cornell University (1963-1977). The papers illustrate the Corson administration reconstituting the University following the trauma of the 1969 student revolt and the negative publicity following the takeover of Willard Straight Hall; dealing with anti-war demonstrations and protests relative to other social and local issues; and surviving the university fiscal crisis of the early and mid 1970s.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dale R. Corson was named chairman of the Physics Department at Cornell University in 1956, Dean of the College of Engineering in 1959, Provost in 1963, and President in 1969, a position he held until 1977.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Dale R. Corson papers consist of office files, correspondence, and other material deriving chiefly from his provostship (1963-1969) and presidency of Cornell University (1963-1977). The papers illustrate the Corson administration reconstituting the University following the trauma of the 1969 student revolt and the negative publicity following the takeover of Willard Straight Hall; dealing with anti-war demonstrations and protests relative to other social and local issues; and surviving the university fiscal crisis of the early and mid 1970s. Subjects include long range financial planning, the endowment fund, relations with trustees, and the improved functioning of the university administration; also, relations with trustee special committees and the many formal and ad hoc university committees, social responsibility and investment policy, the cultivation of alumni support, relations with the University Faculty, relations with the New York State College of Agriculture, the New York State College of Human Ecology, the College of Arts and Sciences, the Cornell University Medical College, the School of Nursing, the Center for International Studies, the Center for Environmental Quality Management, the Center for Radiophysics and Space Research, the Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory, the Human Affairs Program, and the Society for the Humanities; the collection also documents the separation of Cornell and the Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, and the growth of the Division of Biological Sciences.
Other subjects include the controversy surrounding Cornell United Religious Work and the role of Daniel Berrigan, the investigation of the Safety Division, the involvement of university employees in decision making and grievance procedures, the problems of parking and space needs, the issue of minority hiring on university construction projects, the building of the Campus Store, North Campus Dormitories, and several other facilities, the development of the Department of Physical Education and Athletics and intercollegiate athletics generally, and the investigation of Cornell by the National Collegiate Athletic Association. The papers show the growth of the Personnel Department and the reorganization of the central administration, and the relations between Cornell and the Ivy League and other colleges, and with several educational and philanthropic foundations, including the American Council on Education, the Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, the American Association of University Professors, the Ford Foundation, and the Carnegie Corporation. Similar files are concerned with university research and government funded research, and with relations with state and federal governments and corporations such as IBM and Xerox. Topics also include academic freedom and the rights and responsibilities of the University Faculty, representative governance, the University Senate, the Faculty Council of Representatives, and the Office of the Judicial Administrator.
Includes tape recordings of interviews conducted by Gould P. Colman, University Archivist.
Includes employment contracts, and correspondence with Frank R. Clifford.
Other subjects include the development of the Affirmative Action Program, the Africana Studies and Research Center, Ujamaa Residential College, and the associated difficulties arising from HEW guidelines pertaining to the college, and the needs of non-black minorities and international students. Other topics include the emergence of women's issues and programs, including the Women's Caucus, the Women's Study Program, and the Committee on the Status of Women; student dissent, protest, and demonstration, and the administration's several means of dealing with them. There is ample documentation of the takeover of Carpenter Hall in 1972, and the vandalism on campus and in Collegetown; the administration's response to the use of drugs and the changing deportment of students, to the new attitudes concerning commencement, and to the demands and interests of several student groups, including Students for a Democratic Society (SDS). Another issue is the involvement of students in matters of educational relevance, and the appearance of controversial speakers on campus. Major correspondents include Morton Adams, J. Robert Barlow, Mark Barlow, Max Black, Derek C. Bok, Ernest L. Boyer, Stuart M. Brown, Patricia J. Carry, Lisle C. Carter, Van Alan Clark, W. Donald Cooke, Edmund T. Cranch, H. Justin Davidson, Arthur H. Dean, Mary H. Donlon (Alger), Thomas Gold, Henry Guerlac, William D. Gurowitz, Jackson O. Hall, David B. Hayter, Delridge Hunter, Herbert F. Johnson, Alfred E. Kahn, and Robert J. Kane.
Other correspondents include William R. Keast, John G. Kemeny, W. Keith Kennedy, David C. Knapp, Samuel A. Lawrence, Paul J. Leurgans, Harry Levin, Sol M. Linowitz, Franklin A. Long, Thomas W. Mackesey, Deane W. Malott, Paul L. McKeegan, Robert D. Miller, Robert S. Morison, Steven Muller, Floyd R. Newman, Benjamin Nichols, Jansen Noyes, Nicholas H. Noyes, Ewald B. Nyquist, Robert D. O'Brien, John M. Olin, Spencer T. Olin, Charles E. Palm, Kermit C. Parsons, Norman Penney, James A. Perkins, Arthur H. Peterson, Robert A. Plane, Robert W. Purcell, Richard M. Ramin, Gustav J. Requardt, Robert F. Risley, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Thomas R. Rogers, Byron W. Saunders, Andrew S. Schultz, Robert A. Scott, Alain Seznec, Robert L. Sproull, Neal R. Stamp, Thomas L. Tobin, James E. Turner, Henry G. Vaughan, J. Carlton Ward, John H. Whitlock, Philip Will, Diedrich K. Willers, L. Pearce Williams, and Theodore P. Wright.
Also included is a photocopy of the typewritten third draft of "Confrontation at Cornell," a contemporary report by Computer Science professor Peter Wegner on the student protests of the spring of 1969 and the issues faced by Cornell and other universities at that time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Corson, Dale R.; Adams, Morton, 1910-; Barlow, J. Robert.; Barlow, Mark,; Berrigan, Daniel.; Black, Max, 1909-1988.; Bok, Derek Curtis.; Boyer, Ernest L.; Brown, Stuart M.; Carry, Patricia J.; Carter, Lisle C.; Clark, Van Alan.; Clifford, Frank R.; Cooke, W. Donald.; Cranch, Edmund T. (Edmund Titus), 1922-; Davidson, H. Justin.; Dean, Arthur H.; Donlon, Mary H., 1893-1977.; Gold, Thomas.; Guerlac, Henry.; Gurowitz, William D.; Hall, Jackson O.; Hayter, David B.; Hunter, Delridge.; Johnson, Herbert F.; Kahn, Alfred E. (Alfred Edward).; Kane, Robert J.; Keast, William R.; Kemeny, John G.; Kennedy, W. Keith, 1919-; Knapp, David C.; Lawrence, Samuel A.; Leurgans, Paul J.; Levin, Harry.; Linowitz, Sol M., 1913-; Long, Franklin A., 1910-; Mackesey, Thomas W. (Thomas William), 1908-1976.; Malott, Deane W. (Deane Waldo), 1898-; McKeegan, Paul M.; Miller, Robert D.; Morison, Robert S., 1906-; Muller, Steven, 1927-; Newman, Floyd R. (Floyd Roy), 1890-1990.; Nichols, Benjamin.; Noyes, Jansen.; Noyes, Nicholas H.; Nyquist, Ewald B., 1914-; O'Brien, Robert D.; Olin, John M.; Olin, Spencer T.; Palm, Charles E.; Parsons, Kermit C. (Kermit Carlyle), 1927-; Penney, Norman.; Perkins, James Alfred, 1911-; Peterson, Arthur H.; Plane, Robert A.; Purcell, Robert W.; Ramin, Richard M.; Requardt, Gustav J.; Risley, Robert F.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.; Rogers, Thomas R.; Saunders, Byron W., 1915-1987.; Schultz, Andrew, 1913-; Scott, Robert A.; Seznec, Alain.; Sproull, Robert L.; Stamp, Neal R.; Tobin, Thomas L.; Turner, James E.; Vaughan, Henry G.; Ward, J. Carlton.; Whitlock, John H., 1913-; Will, Philip, 1906-; Willers, Diedrich K.; Williams, L. Pearce (Leslie Pearce), 1927-; Wright, Theodore Paul, 1895-1970.; American Association of University Professors.; American Council on Education.; Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York.; Carnegie Corporation.; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory.; Cornell United Religious Work.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University--Presidents.; Cornell University--Libraries.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Finance.; Cornell University--Museums.; Cornell University Medical College.; Cornell University-New York Hospital School of Nursing.; Cornell University.; Cornell University. Office of the President.; Cornell University. University Faculty.; Cornell University. Department of Economics.; Cornell University. Special Committee on Capital Financing.; Cornell University. Board of Trustees.; Cornell University. Center for International Studies.; Cornell University. Center for Environmental Quality Management.; Cornell University. Center for Radiophysics and Space Research.; Cornell University. Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory.; Cornell University. Personnel Department; Cornell University. University Senate.; Cornell University. Faculty Council of Representatives.; Cornell University. Affirmative Action Program.; Cornell University. Office of the Judicial Administrator.; Cornell University. Africana Studies and Research Center.; Cornell University. Ujamaa Residential College.; Cornell University. Women's Study Program.; Cornell University. Committee on the Status of Women.; Cornell University. Carpenter Hall.; Cornell University. Division of Biological Sciences.; Cornell Women's Caucus.; Ford Foundation.; International Business Machines Corporation.; Ivy League.; National Collegiate Athletic Association.; New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center--Administration.; New York State College of Agriculture--Administration.; New York State College of Human Ecology--Administration.; Seeley G. Mudd Fund.; State University of New York.; Students for a Democratic Society.; United States Commission on Civil Rights.; United States. Department of Defense.; United States. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.; United States. Army. Reserve Officers Training Corps.; Xerox Corporation.
Subjects:
Women college students.; Athletics.; Academic freedom.; College students--Conduct of life.; Military education.; Peace movements.; Demonstrations.; Investments, Foreign--Moral and ethical aspects.; African American college students--Political activity.; Investment policy.; Student movements.; Students--Political activity.; College administrators.; College presidents.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the President's Office. Consult the University Archivist. Restriction reviews may take up to a month for completion.
RELATED MATERIALS
See also the Dale R. Corson papers 1963-2002, collection #3-11-2550, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA02550
Videos can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/85
Videos can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/13186
Videos can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/13193
SERIES LIST
Series I. Administrative Papers
Boxes: 1-127
Administrative Papers, 1963-1969
Box 1 folder 1 through box 23 folder 20
Administrative Papers, 1969-1970
Box 23 folder 21 through box 49 folder 7
Administrative Papers, 1971-1972
Box 49 folder 8 through box 62 folder 42
Administrative Papers, 1972-1973
Box 62 folder 43 through box 79 folder 46
Administrative Papers, 1973-1974
Box 80 folder 1 through box 92 folder 11
Administrative Papers, 1974-1975
Box 92 folder 12 through box 105 folder 42
Administrative Papers, 1975-1976
Box 105 folder 43 through box 115 folder 28
Administrative Papers, 1976-1977
Box 115 folder 29 through box 127 folder 42
Series II. Annual Reports, 1964-1977
Boxes 128-131
Series III. Speeches, 1959-1990
Boxes 132-135
Series IV. Ford Foundation, 1959-1973
Boxes: 136-137
Series V. Employment File, 1968-1980
Boxes: 138, 141
Series VI. Tape Recordings, 1973-1977
Series VII. Additional Material
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Administrative Papers
  - Administrative Papers 1963-1969
    - Commentary Report on Examination for the Year Ended 30 June 1965., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rochester Review., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "University-Industry Relations" by W. Allen Wallis., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Board of Trustees, 1958-63 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Stamp, Neal R. Reports prepared for Board; Board of Trustees - Audit Committee; Heald Report.
    - Board of Trustees, 1960-64 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Tuller, J. D.; Todd, Walter L.; Wood, Frederic C.; Upson, Maxwell M.
    - Board of Trustees. Rogers, Adele; Olin, Spencer T.; Schoellkopf, Paul A.; Clark, John M.; Bache, Harold L. "For Confirmation of the Board of Trustees. ", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Board of Trustees, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Bard, Francis N.; Todd, Walter L.; Harriman, Averell; Dean, Arthur H.; Wood, Frederic C.; Syme, John P.; Tuller, J. D. Board of Trustees - Investment Committee.
    - President - Administrative Staff Meeting Minutes., 1963-64 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - President - Administrative Staff Meeting Minutes., 1964-65 (Box 1, Folder 9, Folder 10)
    - President James A. Perkins. Olin, Spencer T.; Morison, Robert S.; Mackesey, Thomas W. "Reorganization of Colleges" by Mackesey; United States Department of State Bureau of Inter-American Affairs; "General Guidelines for Cornell's Future. ", 1963-65 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - President, Retreat, 23 Dec. 1963.Morrisett, Lloyd N. "Report on the Field of Education at Cornell"; "Survey of Undergraduate Education at Cornell. ", 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - President, Retreat, 8-9 Sept. 1964, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Wilson, Robert R.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Keast, William R. Committee on Disadvantaged Students; "Assumptions for 1980"; Synchrotron; Group Housing Plan; Faculty recruitment.
    - President, Retreat, 11 Dec. 1964., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - President, Retreat, 8 Feb. 1965., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - "The Flight From Teaching. ", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - "A Proposal to the Ford Foundation to Establish at Cornell University a Four-Year Masters and Six-Year Ph.D. Program. ", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - "The Future Size of the University. ", 1961-63 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Statistical Report of the Summer School and Other Summer Programs., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - New York State College of Agriculture Proposal to National Science Foundation to Establish an Interdepartmental Undergraduate Research Participation Program in Animal and Plant Sciences., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Thomas R. Nielsen Proposal to National Science Foundation for a Program of Advanced Science and Mathematics courses for High-ability Secondary School Students., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Summer Session and Extramural Courses, 1959-64 (Box 1, Folder 22, Folder 23)
      Smith, William A.
    - Summer Session - Salaries., 1959-64 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Summer Session - Tuition., 1959-64 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Summer Session., 1963-66 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Assistant to the President for Development and University Relations, Robert A. Kidera, 1964-65 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Marcham, John.
    - Cornell University Council - Pamphlets., 1963-65 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Cornell University Council - Manual., 1963-64 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Cornell University Council - Manual., 1964-65 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Cornell University Council, 1957-64 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Zwingle, J. L.; Cornell University Council - Administrative Board.
    - Cornell University Council, 1963-65 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - "Cornell's Public Relations and the Office of Sports Information" by Ben Mintz., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Office of University Development, 1965-66 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      Ramin, Richard M.; Trethaway, Edward J.; Kaufmann, Richard K.; Olin, John M.; Todd, Walter L.; McMullin, Frank B. Ford Foundation; Alfred P. Sloan Foundation; Xerox Corporation; John M. and Emily B. Clark Endowment.
    - Office of University Development, 1959-65 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      Ramin, Richard M.; Bruska, Walter G.; Baldwin, Donald. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
    - Gleason, Lawrence C, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      Hollister, Solomon C.; Gleason, James; Carver, Howard F.; McMaster, Donald. Gleason Works.
    - The Gleason Works - 1865-1965., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Cornell Pamphlets., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Director of University Relations, 1964-65 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      Marcham, John; Kidera, Robert A. Clark Hall; "Cornell in Sound and Light; " WHCU; Bioclimatic Laboratories dedication.
    - Director of University Relations, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Marcham, John; Kidera, Robert A.; Mainwaring, Donald. Clark Hall; WHCU.
    - Director of University Relations, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      Clark, John M.; Eager, George B.; Goldberg, Sol. WHCU.
    - News Bureau. Kidera, Robert A.; Marcham, John. SUNY., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - News Bureau., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - University Publications, 1964-65 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      Arden, Kelvin J.
    - Tuition Reports., 1959-63 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Admissions Statistics., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Admissions - Study of Class of 1968., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Admissions Statistics., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Admissions Statistics., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Office of Admissions, 1963-65 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      Todd, Walter L.; McMaster, Donald.
    - Office of Admissions, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 51, Folder 52)
      Snickenberger, Walter A.; Storandt, Robert W.
    - Vice Provost, 1963-65 (Box 1, Folder 53)
      Winston, Oliver C.; Mackesey, Thomas W. Cornell University Libraries.
    - Provost - Correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 1, Folder 54)
      Perkins, James A.; Palm, Charles E.; Laurence, William L. Laboratory of Ornithology.
    - Provost - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      Perkins, James A.; Requardt, Gustav J. SUNY relations.
    - Provost - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      Hazlett, McCrea; Perkins, James A.; Newman, Floyd R.; Kane, Robert J. INTERCOM.
    - Provost - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Braden, Robert T.; Stevenson, Russell B.; Zwingle, J. L.; Clark, Van Alan; Miller, R. D.; Folsom, Richard G.
    - Office of the Controller, 1957-60 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Peterson, Arthur H.; McKendrick, M. Slade; Atwood, Sanford S. Student fees.
    - Office of the Controller, 1963-65 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Peterson, Arthur H.; Krumhansl, James A. Campus academic plans; WHCU; Campus Store; Board of Traffic Control; Leaves of absence policy; Room and board costs.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies, 1962-64 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Long, Franklin A.; Fubini, Eugene G.; Beyer, Glenn H.; Atwood, Sanford S.; Boynton, Damon; Hastie, John W. Sponsored research; Field projects directory; Research projects.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies, 1962-64 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Long, Franklin A.; Hastie, John W.; Keast, William R.; Atwood, Sanford S.; Thompson, Wayne E.; Goldsen, Rose K.; Hacker, Andrew; Lowi, Theodore J.; Presthus, Robert V. Social Science Research Center; Federal research support.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies, 1964-65 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Long, Franklin A.; Heffner, Hubert; Rogers, Thomas R. New York State Science and Technology Foundation.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Rogers, Thomas R.; Monson, Charles H.; Nichols, Benjamin; Gellman, Aaron J. Experimental College at Cornell University; New York State Science and Technology Foundation; Classified information; Statistics on research at Cornell University.
    - Report of the Subcommittee on University-Corporation Relationships, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Faculty Committee on University Policy.
    - Committee to Select Vice President for Student Affairs., 1964-65 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Budget Plan., 1963-64 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Budget., 1964-65 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1963-65 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      McKeegan, Paul L.
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1959-65 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Barlow, Mark; Summerskill, John. Committee on Academic Work and Interest; Committee for Study of the Freshman Year; Student Government Association.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced studies, 1963-65 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Long, Franklin A.; Lattimore, Paul V.; Sumner, Mary; Seitz, Frederick; Dean, Arthur H. National Academy of Sciences; New York State Science and Technology Foundation.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Long, Franklin A.; Sears, William R. Salaries.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Long, Franklin A.; Nichols, Benjamin; Brewster, Kingman; Davenport, Donald H.; Hornig, Donald F.; Lattimore, Paul V. Synchrotron; Atomic Energy Commission.
    - CURW, 1959-66 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Lewis, W. Jack; Gibbons, Paul E.; Smith, John Lee; Jaquith, L. Paul; Scheetz, Francis H. Civil rights; Cornell in Central America.
    - CURW - John R. Mott Centennial Celebration., 1964-65 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - CURW - Manuals., 1959-64 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - CURW - Annual Meetings and Reports., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Dean of Students, 1963-65 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Davis, Stanley W.; Summerskill, John.
    - Disadvantaged Students, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Summerskill, John; Snickenberger, Walter A.; Buckingham, George M. Esso Education Foundation Committee on Disadvantaged Students.
    - Office of Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1953-65 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      McCalmon, Byron G.; Anderson, Jon T.; Schaflander, Gerald M.; Myers, William I.
    - Physical Education and Athletics, 1961-65 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Barlow, Mark; Kane, Robert J.; Colman, Richard W. Tar Young Ski Area; Synchrotron siting.
    - Student Housing, 1963-65 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Mackesey, Thomas W.; Summerskill, John.
    - Student Housing, 1964-65 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Haughton, Peter B. T.; Murphy, Royse P. Committee on Student Affairs; Foreign student housing.
    - Office of the Treasurer, 1964-65 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      Terwillegar, Robert E.; Durland, Lewis H. Internal Revenue Service penalty assessment.
    - Office of the Treasurer - Endowment Fund Write-ups., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Office of the Treasurer - investment Committee., 1965-66 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Advisory Councils - Miscellaneous. Atwood, Sanford S., 1960-62 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Advisory Councils - Miscellaneous. Cornell University Libraries, Manuscripts and University Archives., 1962-64 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Advisory Councils., 1963-64 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Advisory Council - Veterinary Medicine., 1960-64 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Advisory Council - Industrial and Labor Relations., 1960-64 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Advisory Council - Law School., 1960-63 (Box 2, Folder 35)